

Manuel Smith

Technical Writer

In need of a technical writer that explains abstract concepts eloquently such that even the most technically-inexperienced reader can understand? Look no further!

I write technical and marketing content optimized for human readers and search engine crawlers.

Extensive keyword research is the core of my content strategy.

Let's discuss if I sound like a great fit.

SKILLS

- · Google Docs, Sheets and Slides
- Networking & Routing
- Virtualization
- · Admin-level Linux and CLI
- Python, NodeJS (Express) and C++
- HTML CSS and JavaScript
- JSON and XML
- · Git and GitHub
- Canva and Grammarly

EDUCATION

- Degree in Information security and Technology | Boston University -2019-2022
- CCNA | Cisco Ongoing

WORK EXPERIENCE

Technical Writer & Editor Zevenet | 2022 - Now

- Developed and Edited UX-friendly Technical documentation, drastically reducing bounce rate
- Conducted Market research to understand customer needs and used that information to craft well-targeted how-to guides with the help of Zevenet Developers
- Conducted reviews and provided feedback on technical documents created by other team members.
- Worked closely with product managers, engineers, and other stakeholders to ensure accuracy and completeness of technical documents.

Technical Writer

Cranelux | 2020 - now

- Developed and maintained templates and style guides for technical documents.
- Created and maintained technical documentation, including user manuals, quick start guides
- Updated and maintained technical documentation to ensure accuracy and relevance.

CONTACTS



linkedin.com/in/manuel-smith riddicksmith37@gmail.com



4245 S. Riverdale Rd, UT



www.cranelux.com